Thank you for waiting.
お待たせ
Sorry.
ごめんね
happy.
嬉しい
thank you.
ありがとう
Cafe latte?
カフェラテ?
yes.
そう
Can you eat bitter?
苦いのいける?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Warm.
あったかい
Seriously?
マジで?
I haven't asked you what you like yet.
何が好きかまだ聞いてなかった
amazing.
すごい
How did you know?
なんでわかったの?
Shall we go?
行こうか
A hell of a view.
めちゃくちゃ景色
nice.
いい ね
Because the sun is out.
太陽が出てるから
I agree.
そうだ ね
Today is the perfect day for a picnic.
ピクニックするには最高じゃん、今日
Where should I draw the leather seat?
どの辺にレザーシート引こうかな?
Which would be better?
どこがいいかな?
I agree.
そうだね
Is it okay like this?
こんな感じでいいかな?
It's really nice.
めっちゃいいね
If two people are sitting together, this is fine.
2人で座るんだったら、このくらいでいいよね
That's enough.
十分だね
That's right.
そうだよね
Shall we sit down?
座るか?
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
nice.
いいね
There are lots of dead leaves.
枯葉いっぱいあるよ
Isn't this the person who wears it here?
ここで付ける人じゃない?
Around here, right?
この辺でしょ?
Would you like to try it?
やってみる?
Let's try it.
やってみよう
There isn't.
ないよ
Do you think he's that frivolous?
そんなにチャラい人だと思ってんの?
I agree.
そうだね
Should I collect them?
集 めた方がいいのかな?
I agree.
そうだね
Shall we collect it once?
一回集めようか
Collect it.
集めて
It's about to become a heart.
ハートにするところさ
Isn't it better if there are no fallen leaves around?
周りに落ち葉ない方がよくない?
That's right.
そうだよね
Shall we do it around here?
この辺でやる?
この辺でやろうか
Which way should you make a heart?
どっち向きでハート作るの?
This way?
こっち?
In front.
正面に
So let's make it on the front.
じゃあ正面に作ろう
Let's make half each.
半分ずつ作ろうよ
Here and here.
こっちと、こっちで
Then I'm here.
じゃあ俺がこっちね
This is what it means, right?
こういうことでしょ?
oh yeah.
そうそう
The red leaves are beautiful.
赤い葉っぱが綺麗だね
I agree.
そうだね
Should I choose leaves?
葉っぱを選んだ方がいいかな?
Wouldn't it be cute if there was a red one?
赤いのがあったら可愛いかな?
That's right.
そうだよね
The shape is already formed.
形がすでに出来てます
nice.
いい ね
copper?
どう?
It feels really good.
めっちゃいい感じだね
Once you get to this point, you'll want to decorate the heart part with something.
ここまで来たら 中のハートの部分 何か装飾したいよね
What would you like?
何がいいかな?
Looking for something?
何か探す?
Is there something?
何かあるかな?
Fill it with leaves?
葉っぱで埋める?
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
It might be beautiful then.
そ したら綺麗かも
Look!
見てー
High quality!
クオリティ高い!
I did my best to collect a lot.
いっぱい集めて頑張ったー
Awesome.
すげー
copper?
どう?
good?
上手?
Isn't he talented?
才能あるんじゃない?
Really?
本当に?
Beautiful shape.
形が綺麗
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
It has a really beautiful heart.
めっちゃ綺麗なハートになってるじゃん
There are a lot of fallen leaves, so I want to do something fluffy.
落ち葉いっぱいあるから フワーってやりたい
What is Fuwa?
フワって何?
I'm going to collect these fallen leaves and blow them up.
こういう落ち葉を集めて フワーってやるの
It's so fluffy.
フワーね
Did you touch it?
触った?
Got it.
分かった
There's a lot going on around here.
この辺めちゃくちゃあるじゃん
I like this place.
ここいいね
It's a spot with fallen leaves.
落ち葉スポットだ
I'll go.
行くよ
Try it.
やってみて
Are you popular?
モテる?
full.
いっぱい
It's so full.
めちゃくちゃいっぱいじゃん
Reika-chan, this is it.
レイカちゃん、これ
thank you.
ありがとう
happy.
嬉しい
Warm.
あったかい
Let's eat it later while it's still warm.
あったかいうちに後で食べよう
Let's eat.
食べよう
It's been a while since I've had a date like this.
こんなデート久しぶり
why?
なんで?
Hello, it's been a while.
もしもし久しぶり
It's fun.
楽しいね
楽しいよね
Usually it's just school.
普段だって学校ばっかじゃん
Too much school, too many assignments.
学校ばっかり、課題ばっかり
My back tingles.
背中がチクチクする
What?
なんだ?
Did some fallen leaves get in there?
落ち葉入っちゃったのかな?
Fallen leaves?
落ち葉?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
It stings so much.
すごいチクチクする
Where is it?
どこだろう?
Which side?
どの辺?
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I'm a little sorry.
ちょっとごめんね
Stop it.
やめてよ
There it was.
あったあった
sorry.
ごめん
Did you know what you just did?
今何したかわかった?
You took it off.
外したでしょ
What?
何を?
Hook on the back.
裏のホック
Stop it.
やめて
I'm early, right?
俺早いでしょ
early?
早い?
For a moment, huh?
一瞬、え?
That's what I thought.
って思ったもん
Seriously?
マジ?
It's my specialty.
俺の得意技です
Is that so?
そうなの?
I'm curious.
気になっちゃってさ
I was wondering where it would fit.
どの辺に入ってるのかなと思って
Didn't they take this part?
この辺取ったんじゃないの?
Did you get it yet?
もう取れた?
Did you get it?
取れた?
I got it.
取れたよ
It doesn't sting.
チクチクしないもん
Really?
本当に?
I got it.
取れた
Are you okay.
大丈夫
There may still be some.
まだあるかもしれないじゃん
There isn't.
ないよ
Sorry.
ごめんね
It was already taken.
もう取れてました
It was removed, Reika-chan.
取れてたんだけど、 レイカちゃん、
I felt the teeth and thought they were smooth.
歯がすべすべだなと思って触っちゃった
Sorry.
ごめんね
You thought this person was kind of funny, right?
なんかちょっとこの人、チャラい人だなって思ったでしょ?
I thought about it for a moment.
ちょっと思ったよ
sorry.
ごめん
It's time to put away the leisure sheets,
そろそろレジャーシート片付けて、
Shall we go somewhere?
どっか行こうか
I agree.
そうだね
Let's clean up.
片付けよう
Look.
見て
It's like the head era.
ヘド時代みたい
It's true.
本当だ
There's a place like this.
こんなところあるんだ
This area is beautiful too.
この辺も綺麗だね
It has beautiful skin too.
皮もあって綺麗だね
It's kind of amazing.
なんか すごい
Looks like a tourist is coming to Kyoto.
京都に観光来てるみたい
Just this corner.
この辺一角だけ
Only here.
ここだけね
what?
何?
There aren't many people around here, so I thought it might be a good idea.
この辺人いないから、 ちょっといいかなって思ったんだけど
what?
何?
Reika-chan, before I go back to the car,
レイカちゃんさ、 ちょっと車戻る前にさ、
Why don't you go here for a while?
ちょっとここ行ってみない?
here?
ここ?
It's a toilet though.
トイレなんだけど
I feel like I want to do a lot of things with Reika.
ちょっとレイカちゃんと、 いろいろしたいなーみたいな
various?
いろいろ?
various.
いろいろ
Come here for a moment.
一回ちょっと来て
plastic
プラ
I took it off.
モ ーク外したわ
That's right.
そうだ よ
It stayed that way.
そのままだった
This is so beautiful.
これめっちゃ綺麗だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can I touch it?
触ってみていい?
My neck is stiff here.
こっち首硬くなってるよ
I was also curious about this.
こっちも気になってたんで
It's moist.
しっとりしてる
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
It's very round.
めっちゃ丸めいだよ
Her face is getting cuter.
顔可愛くなってる
here we go,
さあ、
Tighten my blowjob.
俺 のフェラシットを締めてくれ
Can I put my finger in it?
指入れちゃっていい?
Then lick it already.
じゃあもう舐めて
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious.
美味しい
Then I'm helping you.
じゃあ助けてる
I can't do it because I have no hands.
手があってしない
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気持ちいいですか?
feeling
気持ち
good?
いい?
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
I'm still going.
まだいっちゃうよ
Three times more.
もう3倍
Because it feels so good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ち良くなってるからね
My favorite item is Tsurui.
俺のジョアイテムのつるい
hard.
硬い
My favorite item is Tsurui.
俺のジョアイテムのつるい
Tomorrow, the tears will be terrible.
明日、涙はやばい
Tomorrow I will cry too much.
明日、涙すぎる
The legs are also closed.
足も閉まる
Oh my, it goes away right away when I use this.
やべ、これ使うとすぐいっちゃう
I have to do it again.
もう一度しなきゃ
Okay.
いいよ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Okay.
いいよ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Where should I put it out?
どこ出すの?
face.
顔
In the mouth, on the face of the breasts.
口の中、おっぱいの顔
Where should I put it out?
どこ出すの?
Oh no, wait a minute.
やばい、ちょっと待って
once again.
もう一度
A face I saw somewhere.
どこかで見た顔が
I want it included again.
また入れてほしい
He looks like he's about to attack.
攻めそうな顔してる
My brain has become hard.
脳が硬くなっちゃった
It became beautiful.
美しくなっちゃった